[{"pregunta":"Can we breath in space?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Yes","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"No","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Only if we wear a space suit","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"None is correct","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"Do you grow bigger in space?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"No","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"The opposite, in fact.","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Yes","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"First and second answers are correct","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"What color is the sunsets on Mars?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Green","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Red","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"The same as the Earth","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Blue","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"How long does it take for the Earth to rotate itself?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"24 hours","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"1 day","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"1 year","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"First and second answers are correct","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"What would happen to your body in space without any kind of protection.","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Nothing at all","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"It will explode in matter of seconds","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"You would burn, freeze and suffocate at the same time","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"There is no right answer.","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"How much did it cost to create the International Spacial Station?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"10 Billion USD","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"5 Billion USD","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"200 Billion USD","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"15 Billion USD","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"Why are astronauts's spacial suits white?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"To defog as much light and heat as possible","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"They can see better in space that way","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Because white is cute.","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Second and third answers are correct.","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"Approximately, how long is the Milky Way?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"100.000 light years","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"1.000 light years","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"12.000 light years","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"180.000 light years","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"How much time does it take for the sunlight to arrive to the Earth?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Instantly","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"8 minutes and 17 seconds","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"1 hour, approximately","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"43 minutes and 58 seconds","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"How many planets are there in the Solar System?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"9","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"5","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"7","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"8","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"What's the Solar System's biggest planet?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Jupiter","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"Mercury","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"China","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Saturn","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"What's the closest planet to the Sun?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Mercury","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"Venus","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Earth","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Mars","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"What's the Solar System's smallest planet?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Mars","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Mercury","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"China","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Saturn","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"What's the Solar System's furthest planet from the Sun?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Jupiter","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Saturn","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Uranus","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Neptune","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"How long does it take for the moon to orbit the Earth?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"1 day","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"1 year","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"30 days","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"27 days","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"What is a \"Cosmonaut\"?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"A Russian Astronaut","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"A French Astronaut","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"An Italian Astronaut","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"A German Astronaut","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"Where is the Asteroid Belt located?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Between Neptune and Pluto","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Between Mars and Jupiter","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"Between Mercury and Venus","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Between Saturn and Uranus.","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"How many moons does Mars have?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Two, Deimos and Fobos","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"One, Lorint","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Three, Lun, Domi and Mars","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Mars has no moons.","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"How far is the space if we measure it from the earth's surface at sea level?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Espacio","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"1000 km","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"10000 km","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"500 km","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"100 km","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"What's the name of the planet of the movie \"Avatar\"?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Pandora","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"Jupiter","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Nagmes","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Pluto","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"Which one of these movies is real?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"2001: A Space Oddisey","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"The magic adventure of Jimmy","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Planet of the Tigres","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Inside Planet Y","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"What did ET, the Extra-Terrestrial, say in his movie?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"My game was good, you guys are mean","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Phone... Home...?","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"He came to me!","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Second and Third answers are correct","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"When was \"Passengers\" released?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"2001","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"2019","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"2009","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"2016","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"What's the name of the blue beings from the movie \"Avatar\"?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Na'yuan","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Na'vi","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"Tai chi","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Giant smurfs","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"Who's the protagonist from the movie \"Moon\"?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Sam Rockwell","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Kevin Spacey","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Dominique McElligot","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"All answers are correct.","correcte":true}]},{"pregunta":"In the Star Wars Saga, Dagobah is...?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"A spaceship","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"A character","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"A planet","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"A Bounty Hunter","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"When did \"2001: A Space Oddissey\" release?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"1968","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"1998","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"2001","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"2005","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"What's the spaceship name that Joseph Cooper pilots in Interstellar?","nivel":"Difícil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"Endurance","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"Stellar","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Inter V.","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Apollo","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"How many movies does Star Wars have?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Peliculas","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"10","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"7","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"12","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"5","correcte":false}]},{"pregunta":"How long can a person survive in space without protection?","nivel":"Fàcil","tema":"Mitos/Curiosidades","respuestas":[{"respuesta":"They can survive without problems","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Less than a minute","correcte":true},{"respuesta":"Between 2 and 5 minutes","correcte":false},{"respuesta":"Between 1 and 2 hours","correcte":false}]}]